ADRIAN VALDEPEÑAS

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

www.avaldepenas.dev



in/adrianvaldepenas/



valdepenas.adrian@gmail.com



0998-856-0686

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript and Typescript
- ReactJS and Redux
- SASS, Bootstrap, Ant Design, and Styled Components
- Express, Sitecore and WordPress
- JEST, React Testing Library, Storybook
- · Root-cause analysis, teamwork, and communication, ability to work under pressure. adaptability

PROFILE

As a frontend web developer with 4 years of experience, I have specialized in ReactJS and have a deep understanding of the library's core concepts and best practices. I have developed complex, responsive web applications using ReactJS, and am experienced in using libraries such as Redux and SASS.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Zuitt Coding Bootcamp

JAN 2020 - MAY 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Technological Institute of the **Philippines**

JUN 2010 - MAR 2015

EXPERIENCE

APPLICATIONS DEVELOPMENT SR. ANALYST

Accenture Inc.

DEC 2023 - Present

- Conducted thorough reviews to enhance code quality and maintainability
- Collaborated with stakeholders to understand requirements

APPLICATIONS DEVELOPMENT ANALYST

APR 2022 - NOV 2023

- Developed, updated, and managed templates for the Sitecore CMS.
- Provided assistance with configuring Google Analytics on clients' websites.
- Translated designs from Zeplin into code using ReactJS, SASS, and other relevant libraries.
- Ensured software reliability through comprehensive unit testing

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Sqreem Technologies Inc.

SEP 2020 - MAR 2022

- Worked in collaboration with multiple teams to implement a React version of pre-existing applications.
- Developed React components utilizing Sass, Ant Design, and Redux Toolkit.
- Ensure the upkeep and modifications of in-house web application tools developed using vanilla JavaScript and internal XML.

INTERESTS







